BU Records: Office of the President (Abner Vernon McCall), Inclusive: 1845-1981, undated, Bulk: 1961-1981
Baylor University, The Texas Collection
- External, 1936-1981, undated; 3
  - University Aviation Foundation, 1968-1975 (Box 168, Folder 19)
  - University of Arizona, 1969-1975, undated (Box 168, Folder 20)
  - University of Arkansas, 1969-1980 (Box 168, Folder 21)
  - University Baptist Church, 1969 (Box 168, Folder 22)
  - University of California, 1961-1976 (Box 168, Folder 23)
  - University of Cincinnati, 1981 (Box 168, Folder 24)
  - University of Corpus Christi, 1962-1976 (Box 169, Folder 1)
  - University of Houston, 1962-1979 (Box 169, Folder 2)
  - University of Mary-Hardin Baylor, 1959-1980 (Box 169, Folder 3)
  - University of Miami, 1971-1978 (Box 169, Folder 4)
  - University of Michigan, 1966-1972 (Box 169, Folder 5)
  - University of Oklahoma, 1966-1973 (Box 169, Folder 6)
  - University of Pennsylvania, 1972 (Box 169, Folder 7)
  - University of Richmond, 1972-1974 (Box 169, Folder 8)
  - University of South Carolina, 1975-1976 (Box 169, Folder 9)
  - University of Southern California, 1973-1981 (Box 169, Folder 10)
  - University of Texas, 1960-1972 (Box 169, Folder 11)
  - University of Texas, 1973-1981 (Box 169, Folder 12)
  - Upward Bound Program, 1968-1975 (Box 169, Folder 13)
  - Urban Employment and Training Planning Council, 1979 (Box 169, Folder 14)
  - Urban Renewal Project, 1959-1977 (Box 169, Folder 15)
  - V Cross-Reference Sheets, 1960-1972 (Box 169, Folder 16)
  - Vanguard High School, 1974-1978 (Box 169, Folder 17)
  - Veterans Administration Hospital, 1959-1980 (Box 169, Folder 18)
  - W Cross-Reference Sheets, 1964-1977 (Box 170, Folder 1)
  - Waco, 1963-1967 (Box 170, Folder 2)
  - Waco Baptist Association, 1970-1979 (Box 170, Folder 3)
  - Waco Building, Inc., 1965-1977 (Box 170, Folder 4)
  - Waco Center for Youth, 1980 (Box 170, Folder 5)
  - Waco Chamber of Commerce, 1960-1979 (Box 170, Folder 6)
  - Waco Classroom Teachers Association, 1963-1968 (Box 170, Folder 7)
  - Waco Housing Authority, 1965 (Box 170, Folder 8)
  - Waco Independent School District, 1961-1978 (Box 170, Folder 9)
  - Waco News Tribune, 1964-1977 (Box 170, Folder 10)
  - Waco Planning Commission, 1959-1962 (Box 170, Folder 11)
  - Waco Rape Crisis Center, 1978 (Box 170, Folder 12)
  - Waco School Board, 1960-1962 (Box 170, Folder 13)
  - Waco Symphony Association, Inc., 1962-1975 (Box 170, Folder 14)
  - Wadley Research Institute, 1964-1965 (Box 170, Folder 15)
  - Wake Forest College, 1963-1965 (Box 170, Folder 16)
  - Washington Summer Intern Program, 1970-1971 (Box 170, Folder 17)
  - Wayland Baptist College, 1964-1980 (Box 170, Folder 18)
  - Ways and Means Committee, 1969 (Box 170, Folder 19)
  - Welch Foundation, 1960-1964 (Box 170, Folder 20)
  - Welch Foundation, 1965 (Box 170, Folder 21)
  - Welch Foundation (1 of 2), 1966 (Box 170, Folder 22)
  - Welch Foundation (2 of 2), 1966 (Box 171, Folder 1)
  - Welch Foundation, 1967 (Box 171, Folder 2)
  - Welch Foundation, 1968 (Box 171, Folder 3)
  - Welch Foundation, 1968 (Box 171, Folder 4)
  - Welch Foundation, 1969 (Box 171, Folder 5)
  - Welch Foundation, 1970 (Box 171, Folder 6)
  - Welch Foundation, 1971-1972 (Box 171, Folder 7)
  - Welch Foundation, 1973-1975 (Box 172, Folder 1)
  - West Texas Chamber of Commerce, 1962-1976 (Box 172, Folder 2)
  - West Texas State University, 1972-1980 (Box 172, Folder 3)
  - Western Institute for Science and Technology, 1968-1973 (Box 172, Folder 4)
  - Western Institute for Science and Technology (1 of 4), 1974 (Box 172, Folder 5)
  - Western Institute for Science and Technology (2 of 4), 1974 (Box 172, Folder 6)
  - Western Institute for Science and Technology (3 of 4), 1974 (Box 172, Folder 7)
  - Western Institute for Science and Technology (4 of 4), 1974 (Box 172, Folder 8)
  - Western Institute for Science and Technology (1 of 2), 1975 (Box 173, Folder 1)
  - Western Institute for Science and Technology (2 of 2), 1975 (Box 173, Folder 2)
  - Western Institute for Science and Technology, 1976 (Box 173, Folder 3)
  - Western Institute for Science and Technology, 1977-1979 (Box 173, Folder 4)
  - Wiley College, 1968-1973 (Box 173, Folder 5)
  - William A. Badger Foundation, 1971 (Box 173, Folder 6)
  - Wingate College, 1977-1979 (Box 173, Folder 7)
  - Woman’s Missionary Union, 1961-1981 (Box 173, Folder 8)
  - Woodrow Wilson National Fellowship Foundation, 1964-1970 (Box 173, Folder 9)
  - World Microcosm Project, 1973 (Box 173, Folder 10)
  - World University, 1965-1969 (Box 173, Folder 11)
- People, 1927-1981, undated; 4
  General condition: Poor.
  This series includes correspondence and their attachments. The series is organized alphabetically by last name. The last name used to organize the files, in some cases, is the name of an individual discussed in the correspondence rather than the correspondent. Any individual with a folder specifically labeled with their name was a folder that was retained from the original order. All other materials were found in miscellaneous folders and put into alphabetical order by last name according to the name written at the top of each piece of paper. This series is in poor condition.
  - Aa-Adair Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 173, Folder 12)
  - Adams Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 173, Folder 13)
  - Add-Ak Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 174, Folder 1)
  - Alb-Alg Correspondence, 1939-1976 (Box 174, Folder 2)
  - Allan-Allen Correspondence, 1960-1980 (Box 174, Folder 3)
  - Allg-Alt Correspondence, 1960-1979 (Box 174, Folder 4)
  - Am Correspondence, 1959-1976 (Box 174, Folder 5)
  - Ande Correspondence, 1959-1977 (Box 174, Folder 6)
  - Andr-Ans Correspondence, 1959-1977 (Box 174, Folder 7)
  - Ant-Arc Correspondence, 1960-1979 (Box 174, Folder 8)
  - Armb-Armi Correspondence, 1962-1975 (Box 174, Folder 9)
  - Armstrong Correspondence, 1959-1977 (Box 174, Folder 10)
  - Arn-As Correspondence, 1960-1979 (Box 175, Folder 1)
  - At-Au Correspondence, 1961-1980 (Box 175, Folder 2)
  - Av-Ax Correspondence, 1959-1976 (Box 175, Folder 3)
  - Architects, 1960-1974 (Box 175, Folder 4)
  - Allbritton, Joe L., 1960-1963 (Box 175, Folder 5)
  - Allbritton, Joe L., 1964-1966 (Box 175, Folder 6)
  - Allbritton, Joe L., 1967-1972 (Box 175, Folder 7)
  - Allbritton, Joe L., 1973-1980 (Box 175, Folder 8)
  - Anderson, Mary Keys, 1969-1970 (Box 175, Folder 9)
  - Anson, George C., 1967-1969 (Box 175, Folder 10)
  - Bab-Bag Correspondence, 1960-1979 (Box 175, Folder 11)
  - Bai Correspondence, 1959-1977 (Box 175, Folder 12)
  - Baker Correspondence (1 of 2), 1959-1977 (Box 175, Folder 13)
  - Baker Correspondence (2 of 2), 1959-1977 (Box 176, Folder 1)
  - Bal Correspondence, 1962-1980 (Box 176, Folder 2)
  - Ban-Bard Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 176, Folder 3)
  - Bark-Barn Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 176, Folder 4)
  - Baro-Bart Correspondence, 1962-1981 (Box 176, Folder 5)
  - Bas Correspondence (1 of 2), 1959-1979 (Box 176, Folder 6)
  - Bas Correspondence (2 of 2), 1959-1979 (Box 176, Folder 7)
  - Bat-Bay Correspondence, 1960-1978 (Box 176, Folder 8)
  - Bea Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 176, Folder 9)
  - Bec-Beg Correspondence, 1960-1978 (Box 177, Folder 1)
  - Beh-Bel Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 177, Folder 2)
  - Ben Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 177, Folder 3)
  - Ber Correspondence, 1961-1979 (Box 177, Folder 4)
  - Bet-Big Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 177, Folder 5)
  - Bil-Biv Correspondence, 1960-1978 (Box 177, Folder 6)
  - Blac-Blai Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 177, Folder 7)
  - Blak-Blay Correspondence, 1959-1976 (Box 177, Folder 8)
  - Ble-Bok Correspondence, 1959-1977 (Box 177, Folder 9)
  - Bol-Boo Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 178, Folder 1)
  - Bor-Bot Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 178, Folder 2)
  - Bou-Bowman Correspondence, 1960-1980 (Box 178, Folder 3)
  - Bowy-Brad Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 178, Folder 4)
  - Brag-Bram Correspondence, 1959-1975 (Box 178, Folder 5)
  - Bran-Bre Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 178, Folder 6)
  - Bri-Brid Correspondence, 1959-1969 (Box 178, Folder 7)
  - Brig Correspondence, 1961-1979 (Box 178, Folder 8)
  - Brin-Bris Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 178, Folder 9)
  - Brit-Broo Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 179, Folder 1)
  - Brow Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 179, Folder 2)
  - Bru-Bry Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 179, Folder 3)
  - Bub-Bug Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 179, Folder 4)
  - Bul-Burg Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 179, Folder 5)
  - Burk-Burl Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 179, Folder 6)
  - Burn-Burt Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 179, Folder 7)
  - Bus-But Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 179, Folder 8)
  - By Correspondence, 1959-1977 (Box 180, Folder 1)
  - Baines Jr., Huffman (Huff), 1962-1964 (Box 180, Folder 2)
  - Baines Jr., Huffman (Huff) (1 of 2), 1965 (Box 180, Folder 3)
  - Baines Jr., Huffman (Huff) (1 of 2), 1965 (Box 180, Folder 4)
  - Baines Jr., Huffman (Huff), 1966 (Box 180, Folder 5)
  - Baines Jr., Huffman (Huff), 1967-1979 (Box 180, Folder 6)
  - Baker, Paul, 1959-1962 (Box 180, Folder 7)
  - Ball, William P., 1960-1965 (Box 180, Folder 8)
  - Barnette, Dr. & Mrs., 1965 (Box 180, Folder 9)
  - Beckham, C. T., 1969 (Box 180, Folder 10)
  - Bomer, Jim (1 of 2), 1959-1980 (Box 180, Folder 11)
  - Bomer, Jim (2 of 2), 1959-1980 (Box 180, Folder 12)
  - Bouldin, Victor, 1965 (Box 180, Folder 13)
  - Burkhalter, Frank E., 1959-1965 (Box 180, Folder 14)
  - Burleson, E. B., 1964-1967 (Box 180, Folder 15)
  - Bush, George H. W., 1964 (Box 180, Folder 16)
  - Cab-Cai Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 180, Folder 17)
  - Calcolte Correspondence (1 of 2), 1961-1980 (Box 180, Folder 18)
  - Calcolte Correspondence (2 of 2), 1961-1980 (Box 180, Folder 19)
  - Cald-Calv Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 181, Folder 1)
  - Cam Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 181, Folder 2)
  - Can-Cap Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 181, Folder 3)
  - Cara-Card Correspondence, 1961-1979 (Box 181, Folder 4)
  - Care-Carn Correspondence, 1961-1979 (Box 181, Folder 5)
  - Caro-Carri Correspondence, 1959-1974 (Box 181, Folder 6)
  - Carro-Cars Correspondence, 1959-1977 (Box 181, Folder 7)
  - Cart-Cas Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 181, Folder 8)
  - Cat-Chad Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 182, Folder 1)
  - Chaf-Chas Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 182, Folder 2)
  - Chav-Cho Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 182, Folder 3)
  - Chr-Clap Correspondence, 1961-1979 (Box 182, Folder 4)
  - Clar Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 182, Folder 5)
  - Clau-Cle Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 182, Folder 6)
  - Cli Correspondence, 1960-1978 (Box 182, Folder 7)
  - Clo-Coi Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 182, Folder 8)
  - Cok-Cole, J Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 182, Folder 9)
  - Cole, M-Cole, W Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 183, Folder 1)
  - Colem-Colli Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 183, Folder 2)
  - Collm-Cong Correspondence, 1959-1977 (Box 183, Folder 3)
  - Conl-Conna Correspondence, 1960-1980 (Box 183, Folder 4)
  - Conne-Cook, E Correspondence, 1961-1976 (Box 183, Folder 5)
  - Cook, G-Cool Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 183, Folder 6)
  - Coop-Cop Correspondence, 1959-1976 (Box 183, Folder 7)
  - Cor-Cos Correspondence, 1960-1980 (Box 183, Folder 8)
  - Cot-Cow Correspondence, 1960-1980 (Box 183, Folder 9)
  - Cox-Cra Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 183, Folder 10)
  - Cre Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 184, Folder 1)
  - Cri Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 184, Folder 2)
  - Croc-Crou Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 184, Folder 3)
  - Crow-Cru Correspondence, 1959-1975 (Box 184, Folder 4)
  - Cud-Cun Correspondence, 1960-1979 (Box 184, Folder 5)
  - Cur-Cut Correspondence, 1961-1980 (Box 184, Folder 6)
  - Cantrell, J. C., 1959-1979 (Box 184, Folder 7)
  - Casey, Carl, 1962-1970 (Box 184, Folder 8)
  - Cheavens, David (Dave) A., 1959-1975 (Box 184, Folder 9)
  - Children’s Letters, 1964-1967, undated (Box 184, Folder 10)
  - Cloyd, V. M., 1964-1980 (Box 184, Folder 11)
  - Cockrell, Charles L., 1959-1979 (Box 184, Folder 12)
  - Collins, Carr P., 1959-1961 (Box 185, Folder 1)
  - Collins, Carr P., 1962-1965 (Box 185, Folder 2)
  - Collins, Carr P., 1966-1975 (Box 185, Folder 3)
  - Cooper, Victor K., 1959-1974 (Box 185, Folder 4)
  - Cummings, Clifton H., 1965-1968 (Box 185, Folder 5)
  - Dab-Dar Correspondence, 1958-1980 (Box 185, Folder 6)
  - Dau-Davis, J Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 185, Folder 7)
  - Davis, M-Davison Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 185, Folder 8)
  - Dawson, D-Dawson, J Correspondence, 1959-1973 (Box 185, Folder 9)
  - Dawson, L-Day Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 185, Folder 10)
  - Dea-Deg Correspondence, 1961-1979 (Box 186, Folder 1)
  - Deh-Denm Correspondence, 1960-1978 (Box 186, Folder 2)
  - Denn-Det Correspondence, 1960-1980 (Box 186, Folder 3)
  - Dev-Dic Correspondence, 1960-1978 (Box 186, Folder 4)
  - Die-Dillard, H Correspondence, 1960-1978 (Box 186, Folder 5)
  - Dillard, R-Dix Correspondence, 1959-1975 (Box 186, Folder 6)
  - Dob-Dou Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 186, Folder 7)
  - Dow-Doz Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 186, Folder 8)
  - Dr-Duf Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 186, Folder 9)
  - Dug-Duk Correspondence, 1960-1974 (Box 187, Folder 1)
  - Duna-Dunh Correspondence, 1959-1976 (Box 187, Folder 2)
  - Dunk-Duv Correspondence, 1961-1980 (Box 187, Folder 3)
  - Dw-Dy Correspondence, 1960-1975 (Box 187, Folder 4)
  - Daniel, Bill, 1959-1973 (Box 187, Folder 5)
  - Daniel, Price, 1959-1966 (Box 187, Folder 6)
  - Daniel, Price, 1967-1979 (Box 187, Folder 7)
  - Dillard, Jack, 1959-1971 (Box 187, Folder 8)
  - Dillard, Jack, 1972-1979 (Box 188, Folder 1)
  - Dixon, James “Jim” W., 1975 (Box 188, Folder 2)
  - Draper, W. Guy, 1967-1975 (Box 188, Folder 3)
  - Ea-Edd Correspondence, 1959-1977 (Box 188, Folder 4)
  - Ede-Eds Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 188, Folder 5)
  - Edw Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 188, Folder 6)
  - Ef-Eld Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 188, Folder 7)
  - Eli-En Correspondence, 1961-1980 (Box 188, Folder 8)
  - Ep-Eu Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 188, Folder 9)
  - Ev Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 188, Folder 10)
  - East, Sarita K., 1965 (Box 188, Folder 11)
  - Erwin, James L., 1963-1976 (Box 188, Folder 12)
  - Evans, Nella (Nellie) Turner (Box 188, Folder 13)
  - Evans, Robert N., 1974-1980 (Box 189, Folder 1)
  - Fad-Fan Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 189, Folder 2)
  - Far-Fea Correspondence, 1960-1980 (Box 189, Folder 3)
  - Fee-Fen Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 189, Folder 4)
  - Fer-Fic Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 189, Folder 5)
  - Fie-Fin Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 189, Folder 6)
  - Fis-Fit Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 189, Folder 7)
  - Fla-Flo Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 189, Folder 8)
  - Fly-Form Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 190, Folder 1)
  - Forr-Fraz Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 190, Folder 2)
  - Fre-Fri Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 190, Folder 3)
  - Fro-Fug Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 190, Folder 4)
  - Fleming, William, 1961-1969 (Box 190, Folder 5)
  - Gab-Garn Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 190, Folder 6)
  - Garr Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 190, Folder 7)
  - Garv-Gay Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 190, Folder 8)
  - Ge-Gib Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 190, Folder 9)
  - Gid-Gis Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 191, Folder 1)
  - Git-Goa Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 191, Folder 2)
  - God-Goel Correspondence, 1959-1977 (Box 191, Folder 3)
  - Goer-Gooc Correspondence, 1960-1978 (Box 191, Folder 4)
  - Gooda-Goodp Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 191, Folder 5)
  - Goodr-Gore Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 191, Folder 6)
  - Gorh-Gram Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 191, Folder 7)
  - Gran-Grav Correspondence, 1959-1977 (Box 191, Folder 8)
  - Graw-Graz Correspondence, 1960-1980 (Box 191, Folder 9)
  - Green Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 191, Folder 10)
  - Greer-Grie Correspondence, 1961-1981 (Box 192, Folder 1)
  - Grif-Grin Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 192, Folder 2)
  - Gris-Grup Correspondence, 1959-1976 (Box 192, Folder 3)
  - Grus-Gui Correspondence, 1960-1978 (Box 192, Folder 4)
  - Gul-Gy Correspondence, 1959-1974 (Box 192, Folder 5)
  - Gardner, F. E. (1 of 3), 1943-1967 (Box 192, Folder 6)
  - Gardner, F. E. (2 of 3), 1943-1967 (Box 192, Folder 7)
  - Gardner, F. E. (3 of 3), 1943-1967 (Box 192, Folder 8)
  - Gilles, H. Wayne (1 of 2), 1965-1980 (Box 192, Folder 9)
  - Gilles, H. Wayne (2 of 2), 1965-1980 (Box 193, Folder 1)
  - Goldstein, A. M., 1965 (Box 193, Folder 2)
  - Graham, Billy, 1960-1976 (Box 193, Folder 3)
  - Haa-Hale Correspondence, 1956-1979 (Box 193, Folder 4)
  - Halg-Hall, R Correspondence, 1956-1978 (Box 193, Folder 5)
  - Hall, S-Hamb Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 193, Folder 6)
  - Hami Correspondence, 1959-1977 (Box 193, Folder 7)
  - Haml-Han Correspondence, 1960-1981 (Box 193, Folder 8)
  - Harb-Hark Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 194, Folder 1)
  - Harl-Harp Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 194, Folder 2)
  - Harre Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 194, Folder 3)
  - Harri Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 194, Folder 4)
  - Harru-Harv Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 194, Folder 5)
  - Harw-Haw Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 194, Folder 6)
  - Hay-Haz Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 194, Folder 7)
  - Heac-Heard, D Correspondence, 1960-1979 (Box 195, Folder 1)
  - Heard, J-Hearn, 1959-1981 (Box 195, Folder 2)
  - Heart-Hem Correspondence, 1960-1973 (Box 195, Folder 3)
  - Hen Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 195, Folder 4)
  - Hern-Herz Correspondence, 1960-1980 (Box 195, Folder 5)
  - Hes-Hig Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 195, Folder 6)
  - Hilb-Hill Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 195, Folder 7)
  - Hils-Hir Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 196, Folder 1)
  - Hit-Holi Correspondence, 1960-1979 (Box 196, Folder 2)
  - Holl-Holm Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 196, Folder 3)
  - Hols-Hop Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 196, Folder 4)
  - Hor-Hov Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 196, Folder 5)
  - Howa Correspondence, 1960-1977 (Box 196, Folder 6)
  - Howe-Hub Correspondence, 1959-1977 (Box 196, Folder 7)
  - Hud-Hug Correspondence, 1960-1980 (Box 197, Folder 1)
  - Hull-Hunt, L Correspondence, 1959-1977 (Box 197, Folder 2)
  - Hunt, R-Hur Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 197, Folder 3)
  - Hus-Hy Correspondence, 1959-1977 (Box 197, Folder 4)
  - Hankamer, Curtis, 1959-1972 (Box 197, Folder 5)
  - Hankamer, Earl, 1959-1960 (Box 197, Folder 6)
  - Hankamer, Earl, 1961 (Box 197, Folder 7)
  - Hankamer, Earl, 1962 (Box 197, Folder 8)
  - Hankamer, Earl, 1963-1964 (Box 197, Folder 9)
  - Hankamer, Earl, 1965-1967 (Box 198, Folder 1)
  - Hankamer, Earl, 1968 (Box 198, Folder 2)
  - Hankamer, Earl, 1969 (Box 198, Folder 3)
  - Hankamer, Earl, 1970 (Box 198, Folder 4)
  - Hankamer, Earl, 1971 (Box 198, Folder 5)
  - Harris, James G., 1959-1977 (Box 198, Folder 6)
  - Harrison, W. Earl, 1960-1979 (Box 198, Folder 7)
  - Harvey, Omar, 1967-1969 (Box 198, Folder 8)
  - Howell, Hilton E., 1959-1963 (Box 198, Folder 9)
  - Howell, Hilton E., 1964-1976 (Box 198, Folder 10)
  - Hunt, Arch, 1959-1979 (Box 198, Folder 11)
  - I Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 199, Folder 1)
  - Jack Correspondence, 1960-1980 (Box 199, Folder 2)
  - Jaco-Jan Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 199, Folder 3)
  - Jar-Jef Correspondence, 1960-1979 (Box 199, Folder 4)
  - Jend-Jenn Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 199, Folder 5)
  - Jens-Johnson, D Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 199, Folder 6)
  - Johnson, E-Johnson, S Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 199, Folder 7)
  - Johnson, T-Joi Correspondence, 1960-1979 (Box 199, Folder 8)
  - Jol-Jones, E Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 200, Folder 1)
  - Jones, F-Jones, M Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 200, Folder 2)
  - Jones, N-Jw Correspondence, 1960-1981 (Box 200, Folder 3)
  - James, Dr. E. S., 1960-1976 (Box 200, Folder 4)
  - Jaworski, Leon, 1959-1968 (Box 200, Folder 5)
  - Jaworski, Leon, 1969-1976 (Box 200, Folder 6)
  - Jaworski, Leon, 1977-1981 (Box 200, Folder 7)
  - Jeanes, J. Harry, 1962-1975 (Box 200, Folder 8)
  - Johnson, Lyndon B., 1959-1973 (Box 200, Folder 9)
  - Ka-Kea Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 201, Folder 1)
  - Kee-Kell Correspondence, 1960-1978 (Box 201, Folder 2)
  - Kelt-Keny Correspondence, 1957-1981 (Box 201, Folder 3)
  - Ker-Key Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 201, Folder 4)
  - Kid-Kim Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 201, Folder 5)
  - King Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 201, Folder 6)
  - Kink-Kl Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 201, Folder 7)
  - Kn-Co Correspondence, 1961-1980 (Box 201, Folder 8)
  - Kra-Kro Correspondence, 1960-1980 (Box 202, Folder 1)
  - Kru-Ky Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 202, Folder 2)
  - Kilgore, W. J. (Jack), 1959-1969 (Box 202, Folder 3)
  - Kilgore, W. J. (Jack), 1970-1975 (Box 202, Folder 4)
  - King, Martin Luther Jr., 1961-1968 (Box 202, Folder 5)
  - Lab-Lam Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 202, Folder 6)
  - Land-Lane Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 202, Folder 7)
  - Lanf-Lat Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 202, Folder 8)
  - Lau-Lay Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 203, Folder 1)
  - Lea-Leb Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 203, Folder 2)
  - Led-Lei Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 203, Folder 3)
  - Lel-Lew Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 203, Folder 4)
  - Lie-Lina Correspondence, 1960-1978 (Box 203, Folder 5)
  - Lind Correspondence, 1959-1976 (Box 203, Folder 6)
  - Line-Loch Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 203, Folder 7)
  - Lock-Lof Correspondence, 1959-1977 (Box 203, Folder 8)
  - Log-Loo Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 203, Folder 9)
  - Lop-Lov Correspondence, 1957-1979 (Box 204, Folder 1)
  - Low-Luf Correspondence, 1957-1977 (Box 204, Folder 2)
  - Lum-Ly Correspondence, 1960-1979 (Box 204, Folder 3)
  - Lane, Lydia K., 1959-1975 (Box 204, Folder 4)
  - Lang, Aldon S., 1959-1969 (Box 204, Folder 5)
  - Lee, Ralph B., 1959-1977 (Box 204, Folder 6)
  - Ma-Mad Correspondence, 1960-1981 (Box 204, Folder 7)
  - Mag-Mal Correspondence, 1964-1977 (Box 204, Folder 8)
  - Man-Mann Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 205, Folder 1)
  - Mans-Mark Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 205, Folder 2)
  - Marl-Mars Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 205, Folder 3)
  - Martin, B-Martin, D Correspondence, 1962-1979 (Box 205, Folder 4)
  - Martin, E-Martin, W Correspondence, 1960-1978 (Box 205, Folder 5)
  - Mas Correspondence, 1959-1974 (Box 205, Folder 6)
  - Mat-Max Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 205, Folder 7)
  - May-Maz Correspondence, 1959-1977 (Box 206, Folder 1)
  - McA-McCal Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 206, Folder 2)
  - McCam-McCas Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 206, Folder 3)
  - McCau-McCl Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 206, Folder 4)
  - McCo-McCu Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 206, Folder 5)
  - McD-McE Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 206, Folder 6)
  - McF-McGe Correspondence, 1961-1980 (Box 206, Folder 7)
  - McGh-McGr Correspondence, 1959-1980 (Box 206, Folder 8)
  - McGu-McI Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 207, Folder 1)
  - McK-McL Correspondence, 1960-1980 (Box 207, Folder 2)
  - McM-McNa Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 207, Folder 3)
  - McNe-McS Correspondence, 1961-1978 (Box 207, Folder 4)
  - McV-Meg Correspondence, 1961-1980 (Box 207, Folder 5)
  - Mei-Mel Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 207, Folder 6)
  - Men-Mey Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 207, Folder 7)
  - Mic-Miller, K Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 207, Folder 8)
  - Miller, L-Mills Correspondence, 1960-1980 (Box 208, Folder 1)
  - Miln-Mod Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 208, Folder 2)
  - Moe-Moore, B Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 208, Folder 3)
  - Moore, C-Moore, K Correspondence, 1959-1981 (Box 208, Folder 4)
  - Moore, L-Mord Correspondence, 1960-1979 (Box 208, Folder 5)
  - More-Morm Correspondence, 1959-1979 (Box 208, Folder 6)
  - Morre-Morris, D Correspondence, 1960-1979 (Box 208, Folder 7)
  - Morris, E-Morriso Correspondence, 1959-1978 (Box 208, Folder 8)
  - Morriss-Mose Correspondence, 1960-1980 (Box 209, Folder 1)